Heat. Heat.
Hello Kawa
Kawa everyone. How's everyone doing
tonight? Hello. Hello. Hello. Um, sorry
for being a little bit late
but we are live. Hi.
So, today we're just going to be doing
like um
unplanned, unprepared, just chatting,
just wiping, yapping stream.
Yeah.
Hello.
Hello. Hello.
How you doing?
Welcome. Welcome. Hello. Hello. Hello.
Hello.
Uh
oh. Wait a minute. On vertical stream on
YouTube shorts. Uh
oh. Wait. This is bad. This is wrong.
I did it wrong.
The model is supposed to be
There you go. Fixed it. The chat is
supposed to be on top of the model. Hi.
Anyway, so everyone, hello to all. How
are you guys doing? Hope you guys are
doing well. And Genki,
hello. Hello. [music]
So, today I wanted to like just do a
uh Gor Gorelia stream. If you don't know
what gorelia means, it's more uh it
means unprepared, unplanned shrimp. So,
I just go uh [music] do a do something
unprepared and planned impromp improve.
So, yeah. So, uh today I did a few
things. Uh yeah, I did actually do a few
things. I switched uh if you have
noticed my announcement on Twitter,
YouTube community post and uh this god I
have brought back our 24x7 channel back
online.
remember um I have done that uh 24x7
channel thingy as a way to way for
people uh who watch me if they wish to
watch and enjoy like like older old
3 years ago, four years ago jock next
content and everything. Uh you can watch
them watch it um if you want uh on like
a 24x7 station like a channel specific
dedicated for that. Yeah. And I used to
run this on my PC uh last year and since
I came to Japan I could I couldn't uh
continue at that right but
yesterday's stream after um like
watching um
like I was watching Burn Peanut. Okay.
And after his war dog streams, he just
raided his 24x7 channel. And I was like,
and I gota somehow bring back my own
24x7 channel. So, I ended up
um I ended up wanting to
uh find a cloud solution like a host OBS
in the cloud uh and somehow stream it
and everything. I tried to do uh many
other things. Uh it worked. It didn't
worked. Yeah.
So officially we have a cloud server and
the 24x7 channel runs in the cloud
always
every single time. Yeah, I feel like the
internet is a bit bad
for that server. So that's why when you
watch the board like if you go to uh jok
like on Twitch it's Jokix uh hyphen 247
no_247
on kick it's jok7
YouTube it's jocknick watch channel
um so if you watch it you'll kind of
notice like um how do you say you'll
kind of notice like ah the quality is
not that All right. It's mainly due to
YouTube. It depends on the internet.
It's using it's literally broadcasting a
YouTube video embedded in a full screen
thingy on a website or a YouTube embed
playlist. Yeah, technically speaking,
I believe it is illegal and against the
OS. I suppose I think I don't know sure.
I have seen many other people do it. So,
I think it's fine as long as I own the
content myself,
right? I'm the primary owner of it, so
it's fine. As long as I'm doing that for
my own content, it's fine, I believe.
Not sure. Yeah. Um, yeah. And uh today
now I uh had a lot of tasks I had to
finish. And today I thought during this
gorilla stream I thought I'll just
[music]
like chat with you guys and also talk or
if you have any questions if I you guys
have any ideas for me to implement or
anything feel free to let me know like
what what kind of content you like to
watch from me etc etc etc let me know
I'll try to brainstorm together with you
guys and like do it cuz all like for a
past few weeks I've been gaming gaming
gaming or IRL or gaming uh right um so
yeah is this a PNG tuber you can
technically say it is a PNG tuber I do
not have like a eye closing or I
I don't have a eye closing or eye
smiling uh image of this model yet so
it's just a static IC PNG.
Yeah, for now. Hopefully in the future I
plan to get live 2D for this model. Um,
yeah, you'll see it move. So, yeah,
finally. So, God knows how long it will
take, but yeah, as long as I have the
money, I can get it done ASAP. But yeah,
it'll have to wait few uh for a while, a
long while. Yeah.
So, so uh one of the new additions I
have done today while I was in class uh
and stuff I have a system prepared and
everything and a good friend of mine uh
um U had made like a overlay system
which is similar to like the streaming
uh ser streaming um streaming plat not
streaming platform streaming uh chat
services like Stream Elements,
Streamlabs and stuff. Um his service
called Vispo. Uh Vispo that is what's
powering the comments like the chat box
you're seeing the white one on my near
me. If you're watching the horizontal
stream, uh it's the one next to me, the
left side. You're watching the vertical
stream, YouTube short stream, uh it's
the one on top of my head.
Hi. So, uh yeah. So, currently I believe
uh YouTube Koda died. So, I don't have
YouTube chat but but uh Twitch and Kick
are getting logged [music] and uh it
will pass through.
And
all these years I had a all these years
I had like a a local setup, right? Um
let me show you what I have in store. Um
uh one second. Let me screen share my
Discord.
What the I'll go here and
I'll go here and then do it.
That's better, right? Yeah. I'll go here
and do it. Yeah. So, I'll show my
Discord. Okay. One second. Give me a
minute.
Hi. That's my Discord server. Hi. Uh so
um so this uh is a new thing I made. So
um for those who don't know uh we have
like a old we I have like a thing where
I log uh stream chats and stuff and
everything usually. So I made a new
updated thingy uh which will be this.
This was the old one. Okay. Old one used
to have too much like a small thingy and
like um all the stuff you get your own
thread and everything, right? This used
to run locally. I have to run a software
and that will run locally and stuff,
right? But now I switched everything to
Cloudfare. I have a cloud based setup
now. So um now it has Twitch chats will
come up here and kick chats will come up
here chat users every comment you do
everything will be logged now finally
it's a good improvement uh from my uh
streamer bot and Sammy setup and yeah
like it's in the cloud there can you
think about it like this will help this
will help when I'm doing my IRL streams
when I'm streaming from from my phone if
there's any important reminders if
there's any important messages or
anything which needs moderation or me to
look look at it after stream and
everything or after a few years or after
a few months or whatever like I can I
there there's there will be a log right
and I can read it and stuff it helps
[laughter]
I don't need to keep my PC on laptop on
when I'm outdoors and stuff. No, run the
local software and everything. It's It's
such a remarkable um additional upgrade
or improvement. A small little
improvement. Nothing big, but
yeah, it's a it's a it's a and when it
look at the back end of it, it was hard.
I I had I don't know how to do coding,
so I had to
>> [laughter]
>> I had to like keep typing and prompting
and prompting and prompting get it
correct from chatun
chap and it was hard but I finally was
able to make it work. Uh but yeah I'm
satisfied.
Speaking of which the VA
channel is also been it's currently
running locally. So every Saturday at 12
a.m. Indian standard time I have to
change it to GST. Yes. But I'll keep it
IST Indian standard time as you as it
was before.
So that thing is also local right now.
So I plan to like upgrade that old setup
version 1.0 you know, from last year uh
to put everything in the cloud. Yeah.
So, I don't need to touch my water
channel at all. Every Saturday, it
automatically randomizes the playlist
like what content to show like the
sequenced
content, right? All those stuff. For
those who don't know uh how my V channel
stuff works is uh every stream I do, if
you're watching my streams on YouTube,
you can watch those streams. Uh if like
for example you like Valerant
or something Valerant or Apex or
something some game stream and you want
to watch uh only those streams which are
of that specific game I play you can
watch from the playlist available on my
YouTube channel. Right. So basically all
these playlists are being replayed or
play uh like showcased on the word
channel and those playlist will get
randomized. So this week we are having
wait let me check my notion.
Uh what are we having this week?
I think this week we are having let me
see let me see. We're having Gundam
evolution PUBG where wins me than Meta
Chameleon.
Wait, what?
Wait, really? But I I see Apex though.
Wait, what? Wait, what?
What? What the I saw Apex.
Wait,
what? Wait, what?
board amb player.
Uh F12
uh set
set rerun mode and
uh bracket bracket
uh
no how do you do bracket in
rand mode or
live? Wait.
Wait,
wait. Was that muted?
wait,
bro. What time?
No.
Oh, I was muted when uh uh I was muted
when I was showing the Wait, I was not
muted when I started the stream, right?
Please tell me I was not muted.
God, I was
when did I mute? I've been
okay when I was explaining the live mode
of the V player. Okay. V rerun player.
Okay. Uh hi. So um Oh god.
So it's a bit broken but I I'll fix that
in a bit later. It's spaghetti court
from Jaji.
It's fine.
Hi. And I believe my YouTube V channel
is broken because I accidentally send my
vertical. Oh, it's fixed. It's
horizontal. Hi, high. Nice.
I have to be careful. I when you were
explain Yeah, I think I I hit my my
finger hit my mic or something.
It's touch to mute. So,
so yeah, uh that setup is an
inspiration.
Wait, let me show that again. So, uh
I'll show you my reference and also the
thingy. Okay, one second.
Where is Asmin Gold? Asman gold
which
where isman gold is where is this 24x7
channel
where do ahasman
gold 24x7 yeah this one wait let me show
it on stream
uh
wait game
uh uh show the window.
Hey, so Aspen Gold, right? So, uh the
people who are running the Aspen Gold
24x 24/7 Twitch channel, right? [music]
They of course they have the voting
system and everything, which is really
cool. But as you can see, let's play a
little bit. Muted, of course. Currently,
it's full screen, right? So how this
works is uh when Asmin go is not
streaming on his main channel, the Vaude
channel displays the VOD which is ved by
the viewers or random playlisted vaude
that will be full screen. All right. And
when he is live
uh he's live uh I don't think there is
uh
example I can show
uh yeah there is no example I could show
sadly
uh when he is live it it becomes like
the main screen becomes small and it
shows like a schedule then there's
background lobby music something BGM
etc. all those stuff, right?
So, I remade that here. Uh, let me go to
dev tools over here and [music] set live
mode. I kind of remade that here. The
positioning is a bit bad. I don't know
why the positioning is a bit bad, but
centralized play uh video player.
centralized video player on the side
schedule thingy and I was supposed to
put fan art ads and like uh something
something moving on the right side um
but I couldn't cuz I don't know how to
do HTML coding anything so
yeah
so it was an inspiration from Aspen
goals 24x7 channel the person who made
uh who runs the uh runs um 247 channel.
It was an inspiration and I tried to
remake that in my own way somehow. Even
though I don't know coding, I try to
remake that in my own way on my website.
Yeah, cuz uh this basically is like
my V setup is like 90 videos as you can
see. One out of 90. So when the stream
is over, it switches to two out of 90.
So every Saturday [music]
it changes.
Every Saturday it changes and uh you get
a different content. You get and the
schedule will change. Today's schedule
is Metagaman,
where Vince meet PUBG and Gundam
Revolution, but it will keep on
changing. So that's a good thing. Uh so
you don't see the fixed uh videos and
everything all the time. Hello Roaran
Kawa.
Uh we're just yapping today uh and
planned and prepares for him.
Oh, it's really interesting to show and
if I were to give you more into this uh
I don't know why I'm explaining this
again.
It's fun in a way to showcase this. Um,
but yeah.
Uh,
okay. Next up is this. I can show you.
This is the what cycle. Um, this is this
week's cycle. That's Gundam Evolution,
PUBG, Venswia.
These are the playlist ID from YouTube.
And this is the direct YouTube playlist
link
uh which is this. I I don't think you
can see that but yeah and the the ones
which are ticked over here that means
they are active.
And yeah, if I were to remove the reset
the filter, you'll see all the
100 or 80 playlist I have. I think it's
more than 60 or 50. All the stream
contents, games, art, just adding every
type of playlist available on my YouTube
channel will be logged automatically
every week, every day here.
And uh yeah uh automatically logged over
here. Uh
so yeah and you can see more there's
modes there's fixed random sequential
sequential means it will go from uh
board number one uh like for example GTA
5 the GTA V playlist right the first V
GTA 5 stream I did to the last stream um
as ascending order the random means it
will pick random VS and it could repeat
the same board but could not. Yeah, it
could repeat the same board, but um
how is it? Uh how do I explain the cycle
is a bit
uh different as in each V playlist will
have up to five Ws. Even if it's
randomized, it will have five or 10 Ws.
For example,
uh let's say GTA 5 I streamed
uh seven times. So you get one to five
votes and then the next playlist for
example Fortnite or something 1 to 5. If
it's sequential 1 to five if it's random
like 4 6 7 9 12 it's 14 like that. Every
playlist will have a max cap of five
five up to till it fits the soft cap of
30.
Yeah. So five five five. So five
playlist right? Uh five 10 15 20. Yeah.
I think Twitch soft cap was 20 and then
rest of the uh like videos
cuz we need 90 videos in a week or in a
month or something, right? So it's like
um rest of the um rest of the uh numbers
like from uh 20 onwards till 90 will be
randomized.
You you can get like my latest video or
you can get my oldest video. You never
know. It's a random loop.
So there's your
kind of cool to show and
uh where is it? Yeah, this is the
control panel. I guess all these are 90
video ids
and this is a schedule like okay first
schedule is this [music] second schedule
is this second third schedule is this
fourth schedule is this fifth schedule
is random and these are the random IDs
etc and there's the main video ID and
stuff
really cool the show
yeah I want to upgrade this setup to
cloud.
I don't want to do my let my I I don't I
have to keep my PC open every Saturday
uh or something or like or I have to
manually press the button to make it
work in the background and and do the
cycle.
So, it's I have to switch everything.
Do you want to see the code the behind
the scenes coding of this?
Uh, wait. I think I can show a little
bit.
Oh, what the
And I Where is it?
Why is it not showing up?
Oh, yeah. I can show it. I I do it in
Sammy. So, it's basically over here, I
believe.
It's stuck. Oh, no.
Oh, no. It's stuck. Okay. Could So,
yeah, it runs by three stuff, I think.
Yeah, this command I think this is
around
1,04
commands to
get like the URL to be put in OBS.
like it has a lot of Yeah, this is the
old setup but this one has been revamped
and uh the V cycle stuff happens in
these three buttons over here
and yeah this sends it to notion
automates the notion stuff and this
synchronizes from my YouTube channel all
the playlist and put it on notion and
this is the main stuff. This makes
fetches all the videos for my channel,
all the playlist for my channel and
randomizes it and makes a schedule map
and makes a randomized time stamp and
everything. And uh yeah, this one total
max video count, global video count,
all these stuff.
Basically, this
makes it into a whole list of our race
like this. This is like the whole
channel videos.
I think this is like
uh something what I think I have like
100 plus videos, right?
Yeah. All the channel stuff too much.
So yeah, I need a
I did that last year, I think. No, this
was done
before I came to Japan. Yeah, all of
this were done.
And if you noticed, uh I I'm not even
using Sammy at all nowadays,
which is really interesting
coming from someone like me who uh
actively uses this.
Uh lately I have not been using it that
much
and that itself is a improve like
improvement I guess. Not sure.
I mean, it's rare that I use it.
So, there's that.
Oh, doesn't
it's really interesting.
So,
all right. So, coming back to today, um
I had a few things I have to fix. I have
like a few things to discuss with.
Okay, first things first. Uh I think I
need to update my Twitch panels,
right?
And
the current panels are okay. I feel like
uh I mean if it's YouTube um for example
if your language on YouTube is Japanese
or different language if I can uh set it
set my uh channel
description and uh [music] the stuff to
be in a different language. I can
manually set that.
But but for Twitch that option is not
there. So I have to like
uh physically
um like make changes and stuff.
Uh sorry about non pain.
Yeah, it is a bit pain. But I thought of
like um uh like adding like
what happened?
U
what was that ding sound? What
honey [music]
gone?
Uh
okay. Anyway, um, [clears throat]
so what was it?
So, I feel like I should update my
Twitch panels and kick panels to have
multilingual stuff.
That's one of the things I've been
thinking. like I have like a about like
a small short about stuff [music]
section
and everything, right? So, I thought of
like
yeah, it'll be nice if I if I could um
if I could like
change it up a bit and add more Japanese
or something if any Japanese streamers
are like following me or something like
last [music] time.
I just said hi and they took my channel
out. That was Yeah. Bye.
But yeah,
so um I'll I'll slowly do that. I
believe then I think the main thing
which is bending as work
um is basically I feel like
um
uh the website right I have for those
who don't know I have my own website
um
I have my own website and
still not updated
fully So I have to like update
my website stuff too.
So there's so much work to do though.
Wait, there's a new holive unit coming.
What?
A new unit is coming after nearly 2
years.
Marai, what?
Okay, never mind. I got I got
sidetracked. Twitter. [music] God,
Twitter is like a dangerous place.
All
right.
So, there's that. And
uh lately I think I feel like I need to
work on my
been thinking like I need to work on
temptation
like um I noticed that during
collaborations I've been really silent
if you noticed.
Uh that is by hand [music]
and um yeah need to work on that
especially
make uh YouTube short content short form
content and stuff.
So would like it if if you are if anyone
of you guys are watching if there's any
good moments and stuff
uh please do clip even if it's on
YouTube or Twitch or kick even kick now
has a clipping feature so
feel free to like clip
moments so I can like use them cuz when
I scrub through my own word and like
watch through from the beginning till
the end. I'm like confused like okay
which is a good moment I can use most of
the time I just scrub through it and
like be like okay I can't use this at
all but just like be like ma it's fine
not
do this and give up
as a the usual thing
where it [music] happens
And more than doing collaborations, I
feel like I need a
um
Okay. Do more
solo,
especially high.
Yeah.
Uh, and I feel like the perfect moment
to do [music] it is weekends.
Yeah, weekends.
That'll be a good way to like to like
touch grass and stuff.
So, it's nice. So, Sundays are a good
way.
Yeah. Saturdays. think I would want to
stream a game for like 4 hours at least.
Um, hold on.
I would want to do that. Yeah.
Oh my god, my voice.
Yep.
Wait a minute. Let me hydrate.
>> [clears throat]
>> Hey. Um, okay. Now that is out of the
way. Uh,
hold on. I didn't want to yap about
these stuff like what I'll do and what
is left to do.
and everything. [music] But
[clears throat]
hey,
since we're in that topic, I think it's
fine.
M. You want to see how a cloud obvious
looks like?
Wait, let me connect to my server.
It's really It's really cool actually.
Wait, it's connecting. It's connecting.
[laughter]
I have a lot of ideas I could do with
this. Um
since um I earlier showed you guys like
the Aspen Gold uh 247 channel
inspiration I did right right fully in
my website thingy.
So I have an idea where when I'm live
like right now when I'm live live right
this like this
um I can just this on streaming via OBS
right for that loud server [music]
stuff.
So I can literally literally
uh let me show you this
as you can see. Oh my god I think you
can see it right?
Yeah, that's obvious. It's running in
the server. It's a really strong CPU.
Like look at this. It's a AMD Ryzen 9.
Uh wait, can you even say this? Yeah,
it's a AMD Ryzen 9
um
7950X trading 16 core processor and the
GPU is like some RTX 4000 like Quadro.
Isn't this like a powerful GPU uh
thingy? And the memory is just 8 GB. So
that means I can only stream 720p sadly.
That's why the stream is this watch
stream. Yeah, by the way, this is the
WAD stream. It's playing my W as you can
see.
Um,
it's um not that care.
That's why it's like 720p 30.
Yeah, I have to pay like
uh 20 I know 10 or 20 more dollars to
like make it 1080p 30.
That's like $50 of
my hand too much.
We could buy a game with our money.
But yeah,
so cool, right? I have so much ideas in
my mind what I could do
uh to like automate it like um
but the reason why I'm like um how do I
say it?
Sometimes I feel conflicted like
should I do that or should I not do
that?
For example, um
you could
you could technically say that I I do
like look or
how do I say it? Could technically say
that I
um
what do you what's the word? You look at
uh you look and watch and learn how a
creator or a bigger bigger creator does
things and try to incorporate their
stuff, how they did it, etc. And do it
in your own way or maybe copy or
whatever. copying is bad, but also
sometimes it works, sometimes it doesn't
work, right?
Yeah.
So that's why I'm like, yeah, these
automated things, etc., etc., [music] is
too much unnecessary
stuff,
right? But when you think about it,
like, oh, how I wonder how did they do
that? Oh, so I also wanted to know how
how is that process behind it
like think about it today
uh now it's 15 minutes right 51 minutes
I was yapping and yapping I showed you
like my V embeds my jocknik w setup
thingy right did you even understand
anything maybe Not, but you would be
like thinking
um like someone would be thinking right
in the corner of their brain like yeah
that is so cool what he he is doing. I
wonder how he did it. And I when I
showed all of that you'll be like wow
that is crazy.
Too much goes into something like that,
huh?
Everything. But yeah, same reaction,
same odd process
is what I is what I experience when I
watch uh like bigger content creators
when they do things. So innovative
things, right?
like today uh like a few hours earlier
next uh announcement was there they
showcased a lot of they did a lot of
announcements like they're merging
uh the branches of holive like English
Indonesia and JP into one main thing
like hol life they added a new logo
thingy then there's a new gen coming and
talents are getting new updates and
everything, new tech stuff,
holo Raku and what holo emotion.
Yeah, so many things right there the
show they showcase
uh in their announcement today like at
8:00 p.m. GST.
S Tokina Sora had their um new out, new
costume change thingy,
new model like a new costume change.
Yeah, visual update
they call it. Yeah, visual update
thingy. Um
visual update thingy concert. And that
was really interesting.
So
hello Aditi welcome just dropping by
here. How are you? I'm doing great.
How are you?
We just yapping today though.
We're just yapping.
Yeah, we're just yapping today.
So this
wait YouTube chat does work. What
channel link unavailable?
Wait. So YouTube chat does work.
It does work.
Uhhuh.
But
interesting.
Yeah. I'm doing good.
We're doing well.
Okay. You do. Okay. So it go did not
die. Okay. How to fix this?
It shows the avatar but the channel link
is
not showing
here.
for this and
I'll see to that.
Yeah. Yeah. Good. I'll not it down.
Good to see that the YouTube thing is
working. I just need to update the
stuff.
Yeah.
Anyway, where was I?
Okay.
Sh dodge time.
You understand?
User channel URL.
What? I did so many things.
I don't even know how I did this.
Sometimes it's crazy
if you think about it like damn can do
this
much point. No,
I think I can fix the
need to think since I'm live right now
and actively here. I'll just go with the
thingy up right now and update it.
Oh,
okay. I can I can close this.
Let me do that. I'll keep my chat. I can
read the chat. I'll keep you guys there.
So, don't worry. I'll I'm still reading.
But
yeah, from what I can see from my
Discord logs,
chat ID is working, username is working,
user ID is the problem.
That would mean if you're chatting,
how would I check your channel?
Let me check.
I believe
I click on this.
I click on this. Go to channel
like youtube.com/ channel
and UID
user UID. Okay.
Okay.
So, let me just
that
and
put that over here,
you know,
YouTube stuff and YouTube stuff and
working
with it. And yeah,
so firstly the channel URL here is
broken. So I think you'll get
like this.
Yeah, then jog. See you later. Take
care.
Thank you for always coming by and
lurking and talking.
Okay.
Yeah, today's stream is just me uping
and just working.
I wanted to make it as a worked with me
thingy, but I thought I'll just make it
a gorilla.
So, could put in like a just chatting
segment and then
working segment
and wrap up and go sleep by 11 or not
11, 12. Wait.
I'll just fix my YouTube chat logging
[music] setup.
Everybody is fixed now that when I do
idle streams, it'll be working working.
Yapping is cool. Yeah, I barely do
those. I mean, don't barely talk, right?
Um how I used to yap so much back and
then they
Yeah, I'm too conscious now. Or maybe
I'm too shy. I don't know.
Let me do this.
That is the plus symbol. Nothing is
cool.
youtube.com/ channel plus user ID
and what else I need to correct
user
name.
And for the normal embed stuff
and forum
embed
forum
stuff they don't need to share
user ID stuff
like in the screenshot
already
is the channel ID And who's her name?
Right.
Uh
oh. That
that itself is
enough.
Hold up the uh
I mean that itself is good enough.
I suppose for kick and stuff it's good.
I think
and yeah, rest
this for YouTube stuff is working. So uh
I guess it takes time to run and
uh fetch
comments etc. But anyway it works. So
[music] you need a stuff and for Twitch
remember that stuff.
Uh what was the issue with Twitch?
It is fine.
This
is like
the problem is not for the show
broadcast.
I think I can fine. It's fine.
Let's see and wait for what the tip is
cooking us
with. Boy.
and a lady
almost remember the
username.
Why?
Yeah, that's fine. Also,
why isn't that
Why isn't that YouTube
forum stuff isn't made? Is it to
the name? Oh, wait, wait, wait. I have
to check. I have to observe the error,
right?
Oh, yeah. I would have to observe the
error.
I got a
API failed error.
Base type is acquired. Accessory 4
5535.
Uh let me copy this.
I got this error. to
prepare that
whenever YouTube comment comes. I guess
it's
stuff for him thingy.
Yeah, it's good I'm doing this live
testing.
have a broadcast ID yet.
Stream URL. No.
Uh fix
Wait. So wait for me to like this F
for YouTube.
does make use of my stream
streams engine worker KV stuff
and just
look for
the active
broadcast.
Look for that broadcast ID
and that all set to be honest
and that means I can't combine.
Oh, it's going to be more crazier than
my whole database. Oh god.
Those who entering the shrimp confused
what I'm doing now. Let me just one
second.
Uh,
working in the background dial.
I have to make a new heart.
Oh, such a thought.
Okay, let me make a shape.
Um,
what else do we up to? Not that much to
show.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, I can just put it black. Yeah, then
I can put it over here.
Ah,
enough to make it white.
is the
put in the live stream
live streams key
to be honest. And then this way we can
also do the timestamps too
since we have the
garden and live streams
streams
ID
ID.
It's easy
easier I
suppose. And for timestamps you need the
streams
start time right
then we can use
the
streams streams data
data. Oh,
maybe
space
which has in depth
data. of the YouTube
YouTube stream
like this
uh
copy file thingy and just copy that.
I can just copy.
What was the current streams stream ID
again?
I know this one.
Yeah, this one.
This also has the
moral
too.
So we could use that too.
And also
if needed, oh wait, wait, wait, wait. I
forgot.
Does the stream URL work for YouTube?
What the
My no
name shame.
already
published.
have it. Get
this one and get that
ID
chat
chat message. We get
you should calculate using unique time
stamp
maybe
zero cry. She's somewhere there.
Okay.
Stream K. Yeah. Need to bind it.
So then it
and I'm glad I
I really deep [music] thought about all
of this
and damn I'm like now doing it you know
it's good that once you have made
something like a system available
even if you won't use it now but you
have made it
alive you I made something. You like I
made it exist. You can make use of it in
the future.
That's what I learned.
Look at me using my old YouTube data
stuff back and stuff
cuz I made an exist going through all
that
pain and it works.
That feeling is nice.
Baby here.
Give me the full code.
Here's the current
card.
Met the [music] fixes. I wanted
the current code. Okay, we just gave the
cord he
and I suppose I from today's stream
one headache with it.
This is what I made it
cloud chat service thing
chat service logging stuff.
The stealth will be finished. I'm so
happy
cuz all these days I've been putting it
in the back binder and putting it like
pending pending pending pending pending.
And yeah,
out of nowhere I was like, "Yeah, I
should work on it."
and let me be and like do my own thing
etc.
So
okay, what did it say?
Keep normal and use token.
and web.
Oh, it has a has a signature
verification
coin chorus.
Yeah, that will work.
Let me bl this like
I am back.
Yeah, I missed my head.
Look at me already sleepy. Wow.
I need to finish this stuff and finish
the
make it work and finish it.
Alex, let's hope and pray this works.
6.0 Zero version six.
Copy that.
Next test that.
Okay.
Wait. And I put the cord here.
Oh, that's
Wait, is this like a bad cold?
Okay, let's check from my
chef.
Hello. We just wiping and working.
Oh, observable ability. I died.
Oh,
did it? What's the error?
What are you working on? So, we are
literally working on a a where
uh one second, one second.
I'm working on a thing where
um
all this time I had my chat logs locally
done locally, but now I'm switching
everything to Cloudfare.
So basically this
um
one second let me show a bit
uh
one second. Oh, what the [clears throat]
I think it's way better if I draw like
um
for like desktop I guess. All right. The
B.
That's not the desktop I was looking to
show. But
uh
wait, can you see this?
Hi. So, uh this one. So, as you can see,
I used to have like this was my old
setup.
Like every time anyone chats, you get
your own red discord thread which has
all of your chat logs and stuff, right?
I have to keep this software, this guy
open all the time. uh this command this
command with uh 286
with 216 u commands that's how this
stuff used to work Twitch YouTube kick
everything makes your own thread and
everything but now the new version
uh I made it not use web hook uh like
it's using my bot and it sends command
um sends the new Discord uh components
kind of things. It has your uh avatar.
It also has a old thingy and it can give
you the stream link. No, your Wait, why
is stream link?
What?
I need to fix this. Ah, this is wrong.
This is wrong. View stream should not
show your stream. [laughter]
Okay. V channel works. View avatar shows
your Twitch avatar. Yeah. Yeah. I'm
still uh fixing it. U currently I
switched to Cloudfare.
Um Cloudfare all the things which is
done by this guy Sam Shami is getting
done here. So this helps when I am doing
IRL streams, right? when I'm doing I
streams when my PC is not on I don't
have to force myself to keep um the so
background applications on right or keep
the PC on the show um so this helps when
I'm outdoors and stuff whatever comments
are getting sent through from my comment
box thingy that same service is sending
the same relay of comments
to uh Discord
via the cloud. That's the difference.
Hope you understood. So yeah, basically
you don't need I don't need to keep
locally running softwares to do that.
Now it's everything in the cloud. So I
can do I streams, YouTube, Twitch, gig
chat comments are logged. Hi
Uh, we having a delay. My internet is
bad.
Oh,
I had
gotcha. Hi.
I
myself think it's cool.
So yeah. Oh, it works. Okay. Wait. Jok
user channel ID. Channel ID. Broadcast
ID. Yes. Yes. 52. So, if I click on the
stream, it'll take me to the
Oh my god. We have timestamps, people.
We have timestamps. Let's go,
bro. We have timestamps. Let's go. Let's
go school. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go
school.
Yes.
Uh
so what's missing? What's missing is
Twitch, right?
Let me show. So I feel like what's
missing over here? So YouTube chat
thingy is working now. Uh if I show this
um
open channel link now has the YouTube
channel URL. Earlier earlier when
Aditisan was on Twitch the YouTube
channel link was unavailable
right [music] that is now fixed.
Um
like this one it shows the channel
avatar is right now the new chat user
log stuff right here.
Um everything is [music] right and if
you click if I click on this you finally
see timestamps
the the YouTube uh video ID then um URL
parameters here that you have the
timestamps 5442.
So I believe that will work. So if I
click on this,
it will take me to that.
No.
No. Is it back? Where is it wrong?
M.
Why can't I
Oh, maybe this is a live live stream.
That's why. Maybe it will work when I
when the stream is over. when the war is
happening.
Maybe that's the reason why I think
yeah
probably will be working
though.
I see.
Oh, wait a minute.
Um,
how does Twitch
stuff work? I know I can do that time
stamp thingy in Sammy and streamer mode
for Twitch right now, but
How do I
m I think I I think I did this already.
It's just that I'm don't remember it. I
guess
I did this already. I think I suppose I
did.
Twitch chat
old timestamp.
for Twitch. Now, if you were to wonder,
look, Jo, how would you do it for
Twitch? If you have that question in
your mind,
it's basically
what I would do is one second. Where is
this?
Um,
you fetch the
you fetch the where is it?
Uh,
wait. Oh, not this. Not this.
In for the nanny.
This one. This one. Okay.
you fetch uh get user information. No,
no, no, no, no. What you need is
Twitch commands. Uh
you fetch get channel information.
Get channel videos. Yeah, you fetch
get channel videos
and you get the latest video ID.
something like that.
Yeah.
Cuz if I'm correct,
it doesn't give me like
doesn't give me like so uh Twitch works
differently. Okay. Compared to YouTube.
YouTube has a set video ID, right? for
the live stream or a video when when the
live stream becomes a video like a word
where you can replay and watch it from
the beginning and the end. Yeah, it
retains the same ID but for Twitch it's
different. They have a live they have a
video ID or live ID,
live video ID or something or like a
live stream and that ID is different
from when the stream is over and the
that stream gets made into a video or
like a V video on demand V. Yeah, that
ID is also different.
That's why it's like Thai men.
But I believe I
I have
figured out how to tackle that problem.
Let me go to my GitHub
or I think I have done something.
I don't know. It's um
Wait a
m I think I have done something.
I just don't remember it.
What have I done?
What the
YouTube is that?
What? Okay.
Wait. So, I don't put wretch.
What the? I don't put bridge.
Ah, I forgot everything.
Web Studio, come on. Help me.
I did something I shouldn't have done.
Probably
I did this. No, my my my stream summary
website, my page. I already did all of
this. I just don't remember or recall
what I did.
Like it merges YouTube, Twitch, and
kick. It gets the video idea of
kickstream and Twitch stream somehow.
And it did some big brain stuff on
GitHub. Every single second, it runs
automatically.
captures the live chat. For kick, all
the messages gets captured.
And for Twitch,
it does something and like uh figures
out that yeah, this streams video, this
live stream I did on YouTube is equal to
this uh stream on Twitch.
and then [music]
it finalizes that data and then shows it
to my website.
So basically this uh if I were to show
you streams
summary
talk next
what
ah
domix spacereams
stream
me I'm All right.
What
stream summary?
What what
is the page URL name? URL. What the
Huh?
What is the page URL? What?
Stream uh stream gallery. O No,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't find it. Where is it?
It's gonna
No, not there.
Live streams archive. I forgot about
you. Okay. on it.
Yeah, this website.
So, it's literally like this.
You not this. Let's say let me see my
old old stream. These are new ones.
These are not connected. These are only
YouTube only.
Let's take our creators
number
two. Yeah, our creators number two. This
stream should be connected. It's
only YouTube.
Uh, probably this one should be
connected. Not this.
Probably
our creators one.
What the Where is it?
It maybe this.
Huh? Where is Twitch connection?
No way. It's gone. No, do not tell me
it's gone, bro. I did this.
Valerant.
I remember val.
What?
Where is YouTube and Twitch?
No. Where is Twitch and kick?
No.
Hey, what happened?
What? What?
Did something happen just cuz I didn't
check it?
Oh my god.
What the
archive?
I'll give you the idea of this Valerance
frame.
Why is
Twitch tab and everything like
what the
Baka, you're so much of a baka. Oh my
god.
No, wait, wait, wait. It's broken. Yeah,
it is broken. What the Yeah, this
one. This guy. This guy. This guy.
Replay.
I should not show too much uh this uh
sensitive content
sensitive uh
API stuff.
Okay,
that's the world thing.
And this is the filtered.
Wait, how do I even link it, bro? How
would I for [music] everything down,
bro? Or else I'll forget.
Ah, this one. Oh, got it. Got it. Got
it. Got it. I'm dumb. Okay, but I can
show you this.
So we have a thing in the API where
Twitch broadcast V ID channel [music]
title started at duration kick
kick will be broadcast V ID channel
gorilla started at duration.
Yeah. So this Twitch is equal to
broadcast and kick is equal to
broadcast. Right. This stuff over here
is
um
what do you call it? And this stuff over
here is
um somehow supposed to be
mapped. I think my GitHub stuff is not
working.
Uh I have to fix those. My kick and
Twitch archive are broken. I suppose
I go to actions. I Yep, it is broken. It
has not been running.
Yeah, it's not running.
What about kick?
A kick is running. What? Kick is running
even today. Oh, it's been running all
these year, all these months. What?
But the issue is now when I have to put
my cookies of YouTube and Twitch and
check [clears throat]
no not kick YouTube and Twitch cookies
right the browser login cookies I have
to manually put it on GitHub it is too
much pain and I don't want to do that
da
dara half of my stuff is broken
I need the cookies for it to work.
It is what it is.
Uh,
okay. I got the ID. So, connection
ID is equal to
uh today's stream ID. No, let's put this
bound stray
horizontal
stamp.
When you look at it, it doesn't seem
like there is ah there is twitch and
kick. Ah, yeah. Yeah, I see it. I see
you.
check.
Yeah,
it is there. But
I feel like I did some background. Like
I thought about it so deeply now.
That's how I I was able to get this far
over here. Like you have to
I thought of things so much
and yeah.
Okay, I understand. Um it's not binded.
[music] So, it's GitHub who is supposed
to put it back to Cloudfare database.
Oh my god.
I'll tell you a bit later about it. So
far, it works, right?
I mean
have to test
one people. Wait, can someone comment on
YouTube? I want to check if it works for
other people as well
or just my m Let me just
Let me just check it.
Uh, that's the command that I
Wait.
Broken. Oh no, it's broken.
It's broken.
Dang it. It's broken.
Wait, is it broken or Wait, why is it
not sending? Wait.
Also, let me hide my screen. I forgot.
I'm not supposed to show that too much.
Oh, yeah. It's broken. Ah.
Is it?
No. Wait. Does it show up in my
comments?
I'm under short.
Short.
What do you mean short?
YouTube shot. No, no, no. I meant you
have to comment on the stream, not the
YouTube shot.
No, no, no, no. Like it has to fetch the
command. No.
Uh
oh. Wait, the whisper broke. I guess
I see your comment,
but it's not showing up on chat chat
box, right?
Ah, it's not showing up on chat box. No.
Okay, let me refresh the chat box.
Oh no.
No.
Oh no. It doesn't work.
It I mean no it didn't show up in the
comment box like
the thing you see on screen right like
the your your message on the top left
right Twitch and kick work sometimes has
this issue with this this.
Um,
so
yeah, I need it to work one more time so
I can like
this.
I mean, best pun work,
but as long I mean, it worked this much.
So I think it would it be working. So
it's fine.
Oh boy, I guess.
But yeah, guys, it's too much pain in
the show like
I
bound.
Everything is like I mean
I'll I'll I'll I'll tell you why it's so
pain and my head is hurting.
I'll just show this
uh in cloud fair
um
yeah so basically
basically I have.
Oh, wait. Where are you?
Basically this I have this 1 2 3 disco
challen engine stream engine stream
engine notion engine stream API stream
migrator notion gateway
join archive API platform linker kick
proxy orchestrator worker cycle
so many worker stuff for different
different use cases and my brain is so
dead right now that I don't even Oh,
which and what is used for what?
Yeah.
Uh
[laughter]
uh
yeah, it's somewhere along the lines of
I think Oh, yeah. Yeah. I think I get
it. It's platform linker.
I Push
is it?
It's linking platform the show. So it
has to be platform linker.
Uh link to API linky. Uh no this is not
it. Oh.
Ah. Ah.
I understand. I understand now.
Ah. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
So, this was an API thing.
Oh,
link Twitch slashlink kick
slashlink Billy Billy. Oh,
okay. Okay, okay, stand. Okay. Oh,
I forgot.
Last year's jock was really
um last year's jock was really
I mean I mean yeah last year yeah I mean
this year yeah
oh damn
damn I was so smart so basically you
know if you're on my Discord server the
inspiration behind this is actually this
I
um
let me show the card
uh
tonight.
Uh this one.
So, as you can see, I have a custom
automated Discord announcement.
When it's live, it shows this, right?
When it's not live, it change
automatically changes it. It gets the it
fetches the YouTube data from my
Cloudfare and that's it. So as you can
see over here when a stream is ended you
get the YouTube replay which is the
YouTube board link YouTube video link of
the stream Twitch archive link which
currently is put on jockniss I mean
twitch.tv/jn/b TV/Jogn.
Same thing with archives. It just gives
the channel for the Willy and Twitch
and that's it. But
but I used to have it direct [music]
thingy like you get to see a direct link
for the Twitch V. You click on when the
stream is over, you click on the
watch the Twitch archive from Twitch of
the stream and after 7 days this thing
over here will automatically switch back
to this URL over here
twitch.tv/dognet/videos.
Why is because uh Twitch
was right like after 7 days or 14 days,
right? Yeah, I thought about that.
So, and [laughter]
I thought about this so in detail and
stuff and especially when I upload this
VOD,
right? When I upload this VOD to Billy
Billy, I would Billy
video URL over here, right? Rather than
the uh channel URL. So I
think I did something
to like
don't remember what was it.
I remember I did something.
Um
I recall correctly.
I did do something.
So that
Oh, this one.
Um,
no, no, no, no.
Bored.
stream summaries. Yes.
No, this is old. No,
wait.
How is my
what the
uh jo Okay, I understand the vault setup
where but where is my
ah stream archive? Got it.
Steady with me.
March 2026 June
March June
where is what?
Ah this is broken.
Yeah.
No, I don't think this was the guy I was
looking for.
May. Wait, May.
May was this year now.
And I had this set up for the for the um
live streams archive page, right? I had
this set up on notion. So basically
every stream will get logged over here.
Mar June
what the marathon
what the last edit time I'll just filter
this.
Wait, how to filter by last time? I
filled the sword. Did I all
the last time?
Darkness is live.
Uh,
latest
withering waves 10. Hey, that's
Hey, what?
Uh,
wait. Why did it stop after June 15th?
Wait. I I I was in Japan when I did this
stream. What the Okay, so
basically I have manual mode and
automated mode. Okay, so manual mode is
this. I can write the same stream
summary and put the stamps, put goals
for the stream or put add review or add
additional notes. Uh, a good example is
like this.
Oh, wait. Where is that uh stream?
Uh,
where is that shrimp?
Uh, no. Where is it?
My god. Where is it,
bro? Where is it?
Where is it?
When you want it the most, it these guys
won't even work. None there.
Super. H. Valerant. Valerant. This one.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh my god. I didn't even do this. What?
Okay, fine. it.
Broken.
Wait. Fortnite. At least I put Yeah, I
put a dot. Okay,
Put a dot. Okay, fine.
So, these are templates. This
automatically get made every time it I
think I use Sammy for this.
Uh was it Sammy?
I'm not sure.
So it was supposed to be
like GitHub
supposed to work
too much stuff.
Everything is broken.
And the thing with me is that once I
start on a project, I'll keep doing it
till the end.
That's [music] the thing with me
which catches my eye. I'll doing and
doing and doing and doing and doing till
it works out with
that persistent buckle.
Okay.
And yeah, I even had like an AI summary.
Well, let me show this. I even had a AI
somebody over here. This uses like uh a
free a um AI model. It it reads the
stream transcript whatever I said. It's
same thing as YouTube cap close
captions, right? Yeah. I download the
closed captions somehow and then
get it as a text form like this.
And I in this text form this JSON file
or txt file
that gets sent to the AI model and it
will generate me the chapters
automatical automatically gives me
chapter [music] timestamps
and then creates the AI summary.
Yeah, that's why the streamer starts by
testing their audio, welcoming their
audience and stuff. Bro, I did so much
cool stuff.
I did so much cool stuff.
Yeah.
Hello in fourstar 99. How is your
studies going there? What studies?
Um n we're just working and yapping.
Um but welcome.
Yeah, most of my stuff is broken.
He did like
Yeah, he did so many things.
There's an ad on Twitch.
Oh no, there's an ad on Twitch.
Hello, Kellyan.
Welcome, welcome,
welcome D.
How you doing?
really tired.
I wanted this stream to be productive. I
I ended up explaining my old stuff.
Damn.
Crazy.
Hey, welcome back for those who are back
from
uh the Twitch ads.
Hi, welcome back.
So yeah, back to what I was saying
earlier, like I had like really cool
stuff I did, which I believe no one has
wanted to do it because it's just too
much. And why would you do it? You will
ask, right? Yeah. I uh once I once I
have this idea in my head, I'll keep
doing everything
it takes to just go solve every
nook and corner of the problems I will
encounter and brainstorm problems and
issues and fix them all those stuff.
And now everything is broken.
It used to work
my
all these stuff. I mean Japanese study,
language studies, it's going okay.
I need to study more better.
I am struggling with
and stuff and I need to learn them
better.
Oh, also my internet is bad by the way.
You might experience a delay.
Uh there's delay. No.
Yeah. The
But there's actually
Wait, why is the stream quality bad?
Wait, why did no one tell me the stream
quality wasn't bad? But oh yeah, of
course my internet is bad. Oh, sorry.
Oh.
Oh, I forgot. But
uh I forgot. Come on.
Yeah,
my wife.
I'm going to go eat dinner. See you
later. Hi. Take care.
What time?
Oh, wait. It's 12. Oh,
I have to wrap up.
It's 12, guys. I have to wrap up. I have
to sleep.
Um, hi.
I think we [music] ended up just yapping
today. Uh, I did get a few things
working.
Glad I could test out the YouTube stuff.
Um,
yeah, I'm glad that I could test out the
YouTube stuff. It's somewhat working,
but the koda YouTube coder is over. for
the service I'm using.
So I could log chats from YouTube on the
new system I switched today
but old system works so your chats will
be logged. Yeah, on the old stuff.
Yeah, info star c stats are logged on.
Nice.
All right.
Anyhow, other than that, today was a
good testing stream. Uh, like I not
testing stream like good stream. I got
to
um test a few things and talk about some
old things I used to do for my streams.
Most of them are backend like happens
behind the screen. The scenes you don't
see it unless you look it up or go to
website or something.
Um but other than that it was nice. We
talked a lot about things there.
So yeah, thank you again to everyone who
came by.
Um hi
Gorilla streams are fun. Uh I just need
to learn I just need to be more
talkative.
Um, I need to do more. I need to talk
more. Yeah.
Oh, the snap.
But, uh, next time I'll try not to talk
about like the stuff I have done in the
past or these technical things cuz most
people won't understand [music] the show
cuz too much complicated. No,
next time I'll also try not to uh open
like this um like display capture like
today. I think I kind of leaked [music]
some things like some API stuff.
I mean even if someone use to use it
nothing would happen. It's just you'll
get access just to my and public info
data of the YouTube videos. You can just
get that from just doing a simple
YouTube API stuff.
Uh but yeah,
we're really something.
Hey, it is 12. So with that said, I will
wrap it up over here.
Thank you to everyone who came by. Let
me thank all the people who came by.
All the people who came by to their
heart, thank you for coming by.
Rocker Shivan, thank you for coming by.
Thank you for coming by. Thank you for
coming by.
And Info Star, thank you for coming by.
Kalisan, thank you for coming by.
And um yeah, Richan
also came by on YouTube. No, thank you.
And that's everyone. I also got a
for coming by tonight.
I had a good one.
Come. Bye-bye.